Maternal Obsession is a drama, mystery, thriller
film directed by Douglas Jackson.
Her pill-addicted mom wants to make sure that her daughter stays with her always and will do anything to destroy her relationship with men
including getting the guys beaten up, poisoning a dog, cutting herself intentionally and bringing a gun to her latest beau.
Lily Stanler, played by Nicholle Tom.
Inez Stanler, played by Gwynyth Walsh.
Larry Nowack, played by Cameron Daddo.
Harry Charles Salusbury Lloyd is an English actor.
His performance in the Channel 4 miniseries The Fear (2012) earned
him a British Academy Television Award nomination.
He gained prominence through his roles as Will Scarlet in the BBC drama Robin Hood (2006), Jeremy Baines in the Doctor Who episodes "Human
Nature" and "The Family of Blood" (2007), and Viserys Targaryen in the first season of the HBO series Game of Thrones (2011).
Lloyd played Paul Crosley in the WGN series Manhattan (2014), Peter Quayle in the Starz series
Counterpart (2017–2019), and Bernard Marx in the Peacock series Brave New World (2020).
He voiced Viktor in the Netflix animated series Arcane (2021–2024), Z in
Xenoblade Chronicles 3 (2022), and Ultima in Final Fantasy XVI (2023).
He also appeared in Wolf Hall (2015) on BBC Two, series 1 of Marcella (2016) on ITV,
and the third season of the FX series Legion (2019) as Charles Xavier.
Lloyd is also known for his theatre work, earning
an Off West End Award nomination.
His films include The Theory of Everything (2014),
Anthropoid (2016), and The Wife (2017).
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.